Here we go...it's started! This time we are joined by Rika Shimakura from Beyonce Subway and Shiori Nishida from Beyonce Subway.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Yuka Shimakura, enjoy collecting records,
I especially like to collect records from the 80's, 70's, and 60's Showa era,
But a failure happened recently,
What happened?
I made the mistake of buying two copies of the same record,
I see.
I buy records of my favorite songs when I find them on sale at the record store, thinking that I'm lucky,
I've had the same problem before, and it often happens that the record was actually stored at home,
I want to be careful.
How do you store the two records you bought?
I keep one record as usual, and the other one I hang on the wall.
I, Nishida, turned 20 years old on my birthday the day before,
My ambition for this year is to become an independent woman and a big sister,
Project has many junior members, and there are also many younger members,
Project has many junior members and younger members, so I will do my best this year to become a dependable senior member.
I will do my best to get along well with the new junior members who have joined the project.
Let's start with the first part of this year's Omamimi,
Making of the music video shooting for "Angulum: Beasts of Love
The latest single of Angelem was released on June 14.
Here is a sneak peek at the making of the music video for "Beast of Love," one of Angulum's latest singles, released on June 14.
ED]
Yes, now I would like to go on with the production. Let's start with the image shot.
Let's scare everyone before we start shooting.
Please do!
Aaah~
Ohhh...
Yes, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Here we go. Out of my line of sight.
Good start, good start, good start, yes.
Yes, good, good, good. Do it well, camera.
Yeah, good, good, good.
Let's use your hands and stuff.
Yes, good, good, good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Yes, like that. Like that, sexy.
Music video shooting for Ai no Kedamono!
I just watched Kero and Kazunade's.
It's really like Jangol.
It's a very rare experience for me to do a solo rip in a green field.
It's a very rare experience for me.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll do my best!
I love you and I love you
A fiery encounter just before the heat of the moment
The heart of a lonely senior
I'll protect you so much, won't I?
Feel how strong you really are
You've got love on your side, be prepared for it
I just finished the lip scene, the solo cut scene,
It's very difficult to sing.
There is a part where each person changes one word at a time,
I was really nervous,
But I got it right the first time.
That's very easy to do!
Yes, Mr. Katz!
Yes, this time it's about a love beasts.
I hope you can understand it when you see it.
It was taken in a jungle-like place.
This time, we are the dancing members.
We worked very hard on this one.
We practiced a lot during the choreography stage.
Some of the dancers were crying after the dance.
We worked so hard and practiced so hard.
I hope you enjoy watching it as much as we did.
Since this is Takei's last music video
We are all working hard with a lot of gusto and energy, so please watch it as much as you can!
Please watch it a lot and give us your best wishes!
Takei-chan, can you give us a little bit of your face?
Five, four, three, two, one.
Two sticks if you miss it
The First Opposing Campus
Continue to next time
Yes, sir.
Can I drink all of it?
Maimi, I'm ringing.
I'm shooting a music video for "Ai no kegamono",
The dance of this song is really cool,
We're shooting the dance shots at night.
We are going to shoot the dance shots at night,
I'm really looking forward to it, and everyone is looking forward to it,
I hope you will see many dance shot versions of the song.
So please buy the CD.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel.Please subscribe to our channel.
Okay, well, nice to meet you.
Okay, then, please roll the camera.
Let's worry about it. No need.
What's the big deal?
P.I., you're the eyes staring at me.
P.I., you'll get depressed.
P.I., I'd be dead if I kept it from you.
You're the dungeon
Girl It's etched in my heart
Girl It's a beautiful thing
Girl I'm not shy, I chose you
Girl, you've got it all in you.
I want to fit in with the one I love.
I want to be with the one I love.
I want to love you. We are what we say we are.
Kids, the earth is meat, it's farmed.
Use what you want, feel what you want, hope what you hope for.
See, I'm already hooked
Love, hearts, us.
We're on the verge of something special.
We're lonely, we're lonely, we're lonely, we're lonely, we're lonely, we're lonely.
You've got to let the strength of your heart in.
More walking, more determination.
We've finished shooting the music video for "Love Caraman"!
How did you like it?
We started really early in the morning today,
I felt like I really became an animal.
During the rehearsal stage, there were still a lot of things that I felt were missing, like facial expressions,
But now that it's over, I feel like I'm an animal.
I see!
I was a layer!
Then, we should dance together to express our impressions.
It's the last dance!
Last dance!
Thank you very much.
This time, we'll be dancing in Zabanna.
I think I'm in Zabanna, and I've been having a riot.
I've been going wild.
I've been going wild in Zabanna.
I hope you will see my eloquence.
Look at that!
It was really cool.
It was cool.
Everyone had a Beast's expression or face or something like that to match the atmosphere of the song.
Face?
Faces.
Their expressions were really great,
I realized that facial expressions are very important in expressing a song.
The power of their eyes was really strong, and I thought they were very strong,
Also, Angstrom's dance was really amazing,
I was also amazed at how much better they became with the newer songs,
I always look forward to their new songs,
I always look forward to their new songs, and I was really attracted by how cool and strong they were this time as well,
The wildness of the band members is really strong in this song,
I really want to watch this music video over and over again.
That's all for now, here is the making of the shooting of the Angsturm Ai no Kedamono music video.
I love you Sorry for doubting you, rabbit
I love you Within myself, Rabbit
Next, here it is. Morning Musume。' 23 new member lesson video.
Continuing from the previous video, we will show you the lesson of two new members of Morning Musume。 23 new members' lesson.
They passed!
Congratulations!
We are pleased to announce that they have joined Morning Musume。
They have been accepted!
Congratulations!
We have been accepted as a member of Morning Musume。
Huh?
huh?
You're really opening up today.
Did you practice?
Yes, I did.
What did you practice?
What did you practice? What?
Because when he opened his mouth, he said he practiced even when he came in.
When you sing.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Every time you look in the mirror.
Oh, yeah.
Did you do it consciously?
I was very conscious of it.
I keep looking in the mirror.
I've been looking in the mirror for a long time.
You can see a lot of things.
It's not just my mouth.
That's what I'm noticing.
Today, I'm going to review everything we've done since the first session.I'll review everything we did from the first one today.
Ha!
huh?
This is the rhythm
Haa
Stretch it again with this mouth
Huh?
Huh.
I'm going to roll the ball.
I'm going to roll the ball....
This power
Please, mome mome mome mome mome
Let's go...
Loosen up
Let it go, let it go, let it go, let it go
Loosen, loosen, loosen
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Loosen up
Okay, well, I'll just drink some water and sing.
I won't let anyone notice
I'm feeling cold
I'm alone
And I'm not afraid of anything
1D, the idyllic solution
No one can solve it
Even you on the push
I can't do it now
Even if I love you
You know, it's a little hard to explain.
You know what they say about input-output?
Yes, I do.
Which are you better at?
Do you know which one you are better at?
Yes, I do.
Which is it?
The one you think you're better at.
In short, input.
Yes, input.
You're better at taking it in yourself, right?
Yes, sir.
Right?
And output?
That's what most people are doing now.
They have the ability to input a lot, but they don't act on it.
But they don't act on it.
So, why can't we output?
That's the problem.
I can input, but why can't I output?
I don't know why I can't output.
I think I'm not good at output.
Also, what I've learned, I don't know, I'm just...
No, no, no. I'll make it clear. I'm in total denial.
You're doing the wrong thing, but you're doing the wrong thing, and that's why your body is frozen.
They say, "Don't be afraid to make a mistake, just step forward." Which way did they say, "forward"? Just move until you're told to.
If you move sideways, why are you moving sideways? He'll probably get angry.
That's what I'm afraid of. I told you before, praise and stretch.
You can do it with praise, but the next time you can't do something else...
But the next time you can't do something different, you won't know the pain of the fall, so you'll have to be taught again.
That's the point of being a little strict.
And so, as you can see from today's 10th volume...
What? It's totally different from the last time. That's what I think.
After all, people can't learn unless they notice little by little.
And from what they've learned, they can do it again without someone teaching them.
I think that's wonderful.
I think it's wonderful, but I also think that when you're inputting, you're really inputting when you're outputting.
It takes time to become an output.
For example, if you ask me to do something with 00.
I don't have 00 in my head.
But why don't you just do it anyway?
Then I can say, "Why are you doing that? I can say, "Why are you moving like that?
I think of it as a lesson.
I can't give you a lesson if you don't make mistakes.
I want you to make mistakes.
And since they don't even make mistakes, I think it's better to bring that out in them.
That mistake can actually become an art form.
That's what's interesting about you.
I think that's what Koshi is all about.
Here we go!
Want it easy solution
No one can solve it
Even you, older than me.
I can't do it now.
Right here.
This is the part where those simple words like "ah" and "uu" don't resonate anywhere.This is the place where those simple words like "ah" and "uu" don't resonate anywhere.
Because they are inputted in your head and you remember them.
You don't know if it's "ah" or "ah" or "ah" or "ah".
You know that, don't you?
You were told to move, right?
Why don't you use your tools?
If you don't want to dance, you don't have to wake up.
You're taking dance lessons, right?
So why don't you just get the point across?
I didn't tell you not to dance.
You told me to move.
Actually, one, two, three, four, five.
That's not the truth.
You're showing them.
Like last year.
Someone stopped the city.
I'm afraid.
My hand.
It's not like that.
That's not what I'm saying.
If you're gonna get in the car like this, you might as well get in the car with me, 'cause I've done it too many times.
How many times have we done this?
You're holding back so much.
Don't stay cooped up in here forever.
I'll be singing with you
I'm singing
My favorite
That's what I mean. Then I'll do this song by this point.
I can't do it now.
No matter what.
It's all so straightforward.
That's a beautiful song, but
I'm getting more and more confused about what you're saying
It's all too straightforward.
I feel like I'm putting too much energy into it.
I feel like I'm putting too much effort into it.
I have to sing it so hard.
I don't know.
And...
There's a morning song.
The people who sing that song...
You don't have to sing that.
I want you to sing the whole song in your own way.
Of course, when I have lessons...
When I do this with those people...
I don't mind if you do it properly.
But on stage, you can be lenient.
As long as you don't get hurt.
But seriously, please spoil me.
I'll say anything.
I'm serious.
Pamper seriously
If you don't, we're kind of like that
We can only be seen in that way.
You have to be rough like that.
But of course, the rough stuff has to be done right the first time
You have to do it properly.
But to be able to rough it up in a proper way
I think that's what makes a professional.
One, two, three, four.
Thank you for watching.
Now, I'm almost taking off all the rhythm and everything over there, and I'm leaving it to you.
So I have to make up the rhythm in my imagination.
I can't help you with the piano unless you put in your mind how much you have made, how much you have made, how much you have made, how much you have made.
Let's go one more time.
One, two, three, four.
I think you should cut the dance.
Just pick a dance.
I'm not trying to swing a serve.
I'm not tempted to give up.
Oh, I'm not a genius
Davon.
I often put the word "well" on it to keep it from going "zoon".
Tat-tat-tat-tat before dabon, dabon, dabon, dabon
That's the 16th beat.
And the 16th beat is baffling, isn't it? So there are four sixteenths in a row, four fours, four sixteens.
There's one sixteenth open before the da.
So you sing "takatu katakatu katakataka, dabon" like this.
If you can't do that, then you have to do what tap dancers often do, like this one.
If you can't do it, you have to push yourself into the body like this, and then you have to stop.
If you can't do it, you have to push yourself into the body like this.
Piker, tee minor.
Because it's all about
I think it's a pig.
I know, right?
Cut and play, buried hands
Be my lover
Because it's all mine, isn't it?
It's all mine, isn't it?
You'll be fine.
I'm a little sad.I'm a little sad.
I wish you'd let me.
You know, I don't know why you're okay with this. You know, you're funny.
You know, it's funny, but when we do it raw together like this, you get on so well.
And when you say yes, suddenly you're smitten.
And it's a hard world.
I pulled you with a pew.
Now you have to pull it yourself.
Yes, sir.
You have to talk me out of it. I don't want to make waves.
As a line.
Can I put something else in there? Is this one for ultraviolet light? Can I use ultraviolet light?
Ms. Sugai, making waves is also proof of your dignity.
It's difficult, Sensei, to go through life without making waves.
But, Ms. Sugai, if you don't make waves, your life won't go well.
But, Sensei, if you do that, everyone will get along badly, start fighting, and fall apart.
That's why I don't like it.
If everyone is a good teacher, the wind and waves will die.
You can't change my mind with your power. You have to persuade me more.
Convince me with your feelings, not your words!
If you don't make waves
One, two, three, four...
That's the line, don't you think?
Don't you think that's the line?
Today was my last voice training lesson, and I was thinking how quickly it went by,
If you join Morning Musume。 Even if I have a hard time after joining Morning Musume。
I struggled to come out of my shell in this lesson, but in the end, I think I was able to be a little more serious and playful than in the first lesson.
I think I was able to express my feelings in all the singing lessons, but I don't think the people listening to me understood them,
I realized that my singing tone doesn't change all the time and that I often don't express myself,
I realized that I often did not express myself. I would like to exaggerate my emotions more in order to convey my feelings to others.
I would like to put my feelings out there in the final round.
I could clearly feel the changes in each of the 10 lessons today.
I can see that they are getting better, or maybe even worse in some areas,
I was a little surprised to see that even the poor performance seemed to be a change, and I thought nothing would change at all Inoue,
I was afraid that nothing would change in Inoue, but surprisingly, today's performance went in the direction I expected, so I enjoyed it.
I thought that the "Bow Clogs" would end up being as stiff as they were, but unexpectedly, the private feeling of the "Bow Clogs" came out,
When I talked to him about it, I realized that people change a little, and I asked him to make more and more mistakes that I could expect from him in the future,
By receiving these wounds, they learn on their own, and this time, they don't need us to give them anything in return,
They will learn on their own, and they will digest it on their own, without us having to give them anything or make them input anything,
I think they were people who could express their own ideas, perform in front of others, and be entertained.
Even though there are still many things that I have not experienced at all,
What I thought was the most amazing thing about them was their goals when they took their own lessons,
I was really impressed that she knew what she wanted to achieve in the lesson, what she had learned in the lesson, and what she needed to improve on.
It's not something you can do right away, so I really thought that was the most amazing thing. What did you think?
I was very nervous as I watched the video, but I was able to see her singing voice and her appearance, which was completely different from what I had seen in the past lessons on the cardboard,
I was really moved by their efforts,
When I first started taking lessons, I tried to do well and made it sound like I could do it, but now I realize that I was just trying to do my best,
I sometimes wonder if I would be a better singer today if I had been able to take lessons in which I tried with all my might, made mistakes, and had them taught to me,
I was really shocked by the new member who was really great, and it affected me a lot, so I want to do my best too.
This is the Morning Musume。 23 new member lesson video.
I'm sure it will be good.
Well, let's try it once. It's a pretty tough song, so it might be a little tough, but you can skip the tough parts.
You can skip over the tough parts. Let's start with the A melody, as we always do.
This is pointless.
When is it going to be useful?
Well, not much, actually.
But it can't hurt to try.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's about right.
My voice is a little thin right now.
That's all right.
I'm going to try it with a thicker line
Make it a little more resonant.
Inminai konnanshurine.
Can you try it?
No, no, no. I'll take that.
Let's try the next one.
Not much. But it's a hell of a try.
What are you going to do? Pull. Saco? Help me, help me.
200 meters per minute, once you've reached the end of your proximity.
The first two lines are a bit light... a bit light...
I don't know...
Enforcement.
Then, after that, you can go to 200 meters per minute.
Then gradually, 200 meters per minute, close range, end.
I want to end with a little echo.
I also want to make the last bar a little more stable.
Okay, let's just shoot at the end of the distance.
200 meters each, target distance, end.
Yeah, that went beautifully.
Okay, let's try the next one.
200 meters at the end of each target distance.
Eriwan, Mr. Destiny's Traveler, I say coincidence.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I never get the lyrics wrong.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
But, you know, the song started really well.
Yes, it was.
It had a groove.
I'm sorry.I'm sorry, sir.
Let's try one more time.
Yes, sir.
If it ends up being painfully distant...
Everyone, travellers of destiny, let's look ahead by chance and conjure up a miracle
Everywhere, Destiny's Traveler, we'll seek out more life, and we'll happily seek out more.
Everyone, travellers of destiny Let's seek more of life Let's seek more of happiness
I'm feeling good, even if it's useless
That's how it ended up, I was happy, I was happy, I wanted you to laugh
Life's all about wanting more, more, more, more
I mean, what's the point of singing over a 16-bit beat that can't be ridden?
If you don't sing on a 16 beat that you can ride, you can't sing on a 16 beat that you can't ride
If you don't sing with a 16 beat that can be ridden, the audience won't be able to listen comfortably.
Yes, that's right.
It's not just because it's 16 beats that it's good.
A little more.
A little more
I think there are things that can be improved.
There are some things I'm sticking in.
You have to be a little bit more conscious of the backbeat.
Be aware of the backbeat.
I'm trying not to make it too hard.
Don't be too hard on the back beat, and let the back white come out.
Did you think that was a good idea?
Yes, thank you.
How's the world?
Well, try it on the screen.
In this world, there are few right answers. Everyone is wrong, but now...
We're here now. Hanamaru. Hanamaru.
It's so nice. It's so nice. It's like a musical.
Hanamaru!
Aaah! I'm tempted to say "Hanamaru!
Ha-ha-ha!
It's going up and up and up and up?
Ha ha ha ha!
Maybe save one for yourself?
Ahahahahaha!
OK, we're done! Thank you very much!
Motomuya and Fate's Traveler is a very up-tempo, catchy, and fun song that would be a lot of fun to play live.
But this song has a very tight rhythm and is very difficult to play.
When you were asked to lighten the rhythm, you were able to do it immediately.
I'm so proud of you, Kurumi!
As expected of Kurumi Takase.
I thought, "That's just like Kurumi Takase!
I've been seeing more concerts recently where I can call out to the audience.
I think it's a very fun song.
I think it's a really fun song.
In this video, Kurumi Takase is really recording with Wakiyayashi.
I thought she looked like Kurumi Takase.
Her voice is very mature and energetic.
Sometimes I thought she sounded like a singing sister.
On the other hand, Kurumi Takase also has a cute young voice.
I thought it was great that I could hear so many different kinds of voices.
I'm really proud of the members.
That's all for Beyonce Kurumi Takase's vocal recording of "Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler"!
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't
I wouldn't kiss you at the event choke
I couldn't even tell you
Pride Bright July 12th On Scion
Don't worry, we'll manage
It's time to say goodbye to the past, and now it's time to say goodbye to the past, and now it's time to say goodbye to the past, and now it's time to say goodbye to the past, and now it's time to say goodbye to the past.
I've been watching the making of Angstrom's "Ai no Kedamono" music video, and I've been thinking that behind the scenes of such a cool music video, all the members seem to be getting along so well and having a lot of fun.
I enjoyed seeing the charms that you can't see only in the music videos. I really enjoyed the vocal lessons of the two members of Morning Musume '13.
It reminded me of the lessons I took when I first joined the group, and it made me feel like I need to work harder too.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time upcami's partners are Rika Shimakura from Beyonce Subway and Shiori Nishida from Beyonce Subway.
Bye bye!
Next time on Upokami
Morning Musume。 23 new member's dance lesson
And
We will be releasing the decoding of the continuation of Tsubaki Factory's song Seventh Blossom.
Please look forward to it!
Please subscribe to our channel!